六块钱
Six dollars, please.
六块  我才租了一个晚上  是三块钱
Six? I just had it for one night. It's three.
八点钟结算  现在八点两分了
Eight o'clock's the cutoff. And, oh, it's 8:02.
不知道为什么  你的权力好像太大了
You know, in a weird way, you have too much power.
你得帮帮我  我只有三块钱
Look, you have to help me out here because I only have three.
我可以帮忙
I can help with that.
我的天  理查德
Oh, my God. Richard?
你嘴唇上面秃了
Your lip went bald.
谢谢
Thanks.
你气色很好
You look great!
才怪
Right.
不  真的  你...
No, you do. You just...
什么
What?
你的内裤黏在腿上了
You got panties stuck to your leg.
我刚才从烘干机里
That's because I was just grabbing
拿出衣服  这是静电
some things out of the dryer, and static cling.
也许老天爷知道我会碰到你
Or maybe it just cause God knew I'd be running into you
觉得这是个机会
and saw an opportunity.
见到你真高兴
It's good to see you.
我也是
It's good to see you too.
看到那家伙没有  他现在看的是经典片
See that guy? He's in "Classics" now...
不过等我们一走  他就会马上去逛色情片
but you know as soon as we leave, he's going straight to the porn.
到时候他会租《公民凯恩》
He's gonna go up to the counter with Citizen Kane,
《迷魂记》和《发条性》
Vertigo and Clockwork Orgy.
这样真好
This is nice.
-我好怀念这种时光  -我也是
- I miss this. - Yeah.
想一起吃个汉堡什么的吗
So you want to get a hamburger or something?
我不知道这样好不好
I don't know if that's a good idea.
只是朋友嘛  我保证不会毛手毛脚
Just friends. I won't grope you. I promise.
我觉得太快了
I think it's too soon.
不会太快  我十一点吃的午餐
No, it's not too soon. I had lunch at 11.
好啊
Yeah, baby!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
做巧克力牛奶  想喝吗
Making chocolate milk. You want some?
不  谢了  我已经29岁了
No, thanks. I'm 29.
我的天  我得上班了
Oh, my God! I gotta go to work!
亲爱的  你今晚几点下班
Sweety, what time will you think you could get off tonight?
我不知道  亲爱的  可能会很晚
Oh, I don't know, honey. It could be really late.
拜托  怎么又这样
Come on, not again!
对不起  我们做个交易好吗
I know. I'm sorry. I'll make a deal with you, okay?
只要你在我回家以前睡着
Every night that you're asleep before I get home from work,
我就用你以前很喜欢的方法叫你起床
I will wake you up in a way that has proved very popular in the past.
如果你要加班  我很愿意支持你
Well, if you need to stay late, I want to be supportive of that.
瞧你  你什么时候开始溜冰了
Look at you. Since when do you rollerblade?
明天开始
Since tomorrow.
我在公园遇到一个帅哥
I met this really cute guy in the park.
他喜欢慢跑  溜冰和游泳  我们说好了
And he like you know jogs and blades and swims and so we made a deal.
他要教我各种运动
He's gonna teach me how to do all sorts of jock stuff.
-那你要如何回报他  -我会让他达到目的
- And what are you gonna do for him? - I'm gonna let him.
-很好  -酷
- Okay. - Cool.
早安
Good morning.
有人昨晚很晚才回来哦
Somebody got in late last night.
这个嘛  我碰到理查德了
Yeah, well, I ran into Richard.
什么时候的事
When did this happen?
大概八点两分
Around 8:02.
我们聊了一会儿
We talked for a little while,
然后一起吃了个单纯的汉堡
and then we went out for an innocent burger.
没有所谓"单纯的汉堡"
There's no such thing as an "innocent burger."
-你还会跟他见面吗  -明天晚上
- Are you gonna see him again? - Tomorrow night.
莫妮卡  你这是在干什么
Monica, what are you doing?
她花了六个月才忘记他
She spent the last six months getting over him...
现在她庆祝的方式就是跟他约会
and now she's celebrating that by going on a date with him.
这不是约会  好吗
It's not a date, okay?
我要教他做千层面
I'm just gonna teach him how to make a lasagna
他有个自带食物的聚餐
for some potluck dinner he has.
最好多做一点
You might want to make a little extra,
做爱之后会很饿的
because you'll probably be hungry after the sex.
我们不会上床的
We're not gonna have sex.
一切照旧  他还是不要孩子
Okay? Nothing's changed here. He still doesn't want children,
我还是想要孩子
and I still do.
所以我们只能当朋友
So that's why we're gonna just be friends.
炮友
Naked friends.
-你有冰吗  -打开冰箱自己看
- Do you have any ice? - Check the freezer.
如果没有  那大概就是用完了
If there's none in there, we're probably out.
你刚下班吗  很晚了
Are you just getting home from work? It's late.
我知道  不过今天实在太棒了
Yeah, I know. I had the greatest day, though.
我有幸与卡文·克莱的销售代表开会
I got to sit in on the meeting with the reps from Calvin Klein.
我告诉上司  我看中一款性感内衣
I told my boss I liked this line of lingerie.
她就订了很多  你呢
She ordered a ton of it. How was your day?
我发现我可以光用舌头就数完所有牙齿
I discovered I'm able to count all my teeth using just my tongue.
你把一本《闪灵》放在冰箱里干嘛
Why do you have a copy of The Shining in your freezer?
我昨晚越看越害怕  就...
I was reading it last night and I got scared, so....
把书放进冰箱你就安全了吗
But you're safe from it if it's in the freezer?
至少安全一点
Well, safer.
我每次看《闪灵》
I mean I never start reading The Shining...
都要先确定冰箱里有地方放
without making sure we got plenty room in the freezer.
你常看这本书吗
How often do you read it?
你从不把一本书一看再看吗
Haven't you ever read the same book over and over again?
《小妇人》我看了好几次
I guess I've read Little Women more than once.
那可是名著  《闪灵》哪里好看
But I mean that's a classic. What's so great about The Shining?
瑞秋  你应该问《闪灵》有哪里不好看
The question should be, Rach, what is not so great about The Shining?
答案是"没有"  知道吗
Okay? And the answer would be, "nothing." All right?
这是有史以来最恐怖的书
This is like the scariest book ever.
一定比你的经典作品好看多了
I bet it's way better than that classic of yours.
好吧
Okay.
我们走着瞧  好吗
We'll just see about that, okay?
我看《闪灵》
I will read The Shining,
你看《小妇人》
and you will read Little Women.
好  没问题
All right, you got it.
-好  -好的
- All right. - Okay.
-好的  -瑞秋  这些小妇人
- Okay. - Now, Rach, these little women....
到底有多小
How little are they?
会不会小得很恐怖
I mean, are they, like, scary little?
钱德勒  罗斯  这是罗伯特
Chandler, Ross? This is Robert.
你这里沾了口红
You have lipstick right here.
没关系  那是我的口红  我们刚才接吻了
That's okay, it's mine. We just kissed.
穿短裤在外面走有点冷吧
So isn't it a bit cold out for shorts?
我是加州人
Well, I'm from California.
对  有时候你们加州人会自燃
Right. Sometimes you guys just burst into flame.
我起来了  我起来了
I'm up. I'm up. I've gotten up now.
有人要点什么吗
Anybody want anything?
-我要咖啡  -一样
- I'll have coffee. - Me too.
三杯吧
Make that three.
罗斯  你跟我来吧
Okay, Ross, why don't you come with me?
怎么了  怎么回事
What's the matter with you? What's going on?
罗伯特出来了
Robert's coming out.
什么意思  同性恋出柜吗
What do you mean? Is he gay?
他就快从短裤里掉出来了
He's coming out of his shorts.
什么
What?
这家伙露点了
The man is showing brain.
你确定吗  等一下
Are you sure? Hold on.
对不起  你们点的是咖啡和...
I'm sorry you guys. That was a coffee and a....
咖啡  我们可以写下来
Coffee. We could write it down.
不  不用了
No, no. That won't be necessary.
-怎么样  -没错
- Well? - Yeah.
我们该怎么办
What do we do? What do we do?
我想只能尽量不要用正眼看
Well, I suppose we just try to not look directly at it.
就像日蚀一样
Like an eclipse.
如果今晚有人称赞我的手艺  我该怎么说
When people compliment me on my cooking tonight, what do I say?
你说"多谢夸奖"  然后买礼物酬谢我
You say, "Thank you very much." Then you buy me something pretty.
来  我们把手放进这个碗里
Come on, we're gonna put our hands in this bowl...
然后开始把番茄压碎
and we're gonna start squishing the tomatoes.
感觉怪怪的
This feels very weird.
你整天摸人家的眼球  还说这感觉怪
You touch people's eyeballs every day and this feels weird?
我当然要摸人家的眼球
Sure, I touch them.
但我好不容易才学会了不捏碎它们
But I spent years learning not to squish them.
那是我的手
That's my hand.
好了
Okay.
-继续压  -番茄吱吱响
- Keep squishing. - The tomatoes are squishing.
老天  你的衬衫沾到了
Gosh, you got some on your shirt.
等一下
Hold on a second.
马上抹点苏打水上去
Just put a little club soda on it. Get to it right away.
应该
It should do...
就可以了
the trick.
怎么了
What?
你裤子上也沾到了
You've got some on your pants.
干脆丢掉算了
I'll just throw them out.
这些小妇人
These little women!
你喜欢吗
You're liking it?
喜欢  艾美刚烧了乔的稿子
Oh, yeah. Amy just burned Jo's manuscript.
我看他永远不会原谅她
I don't see how he could ever forgive her.
乔是女的  是乔瑟芬的简称
Jo's a girl. It's short for Josephine.
但乔喜欢劳瑞
But Jo's got a crush on Laurie.
你是说这是女同性恋
You mean it's like a girl-girl thing?
《闪灵》里就差这样了
That is the one thing missing from The Shining.
不  其实劳瑞是男的
No, actually, Laurie's a boy.
难怪瑞秋要看这么多遍
No wonder Rachel had to read this so many times.
篮球好玩吗
How'd the basketball go?
我学会了篮板球  罚球和23分球
Okay, I learned how to shoot a lay-up, a foul shot, and a 23-pointer.
你是说三分球吧
You mean a 3-pointer?
我姿势优美  可以多几分
I get more because I'm dainty.
这里有没有电话可以查留言
So is there a phone here I can check my messages?
在后面  要硬币吗
Yeah, in the back. Do you want a quarter?
不用  谢谢  我一向在袜子里藏一个
Oh, no, thanks. I always carry one in my sock.
你干嘛  回去那边坐
What are you doing? Get back over on your side of the...
哎哟喂
Hello!
我是乔伊  我们还没见过面
I'm Joey. We haven't met.
很高兴认识你  我是罗伯特
Hi, good to meet you. Robert.
怎么了
What?
怎么了  你们怎么回事
What? You guys, what is going on?
你们不喜欢罗伯特吗
Do you not like Robert?
你们笑什么
Why are you laughing?
冷静点  用不着激动
Calm down. There's no reason to get testy.
-你们怎么回事嘛  -对不起
- You guys! Come on! - We're sorry.
只不过你的罗伯特的短裤
It just seems that Robert isn't as concealed in the shorts area...
有点走光
as one may have hoped.
什么意思
What do you mean?
罗伯特  把饼干递给我好吗
Robert, could you pass me those cookies?
没问题
Sure.
他们喜不喜欢千层面
So how'd the lasagna go over?
真的  很好  现在你欠我三件礼物了
Really? Good. So you owe me three pretty things.
我一直在想着你的事
I've been thinking a lot about you too.
不  这种"破拉图"交往很不容易
Well, no. It's hard, this "platonomy" thing.
这是一个词
It's a word.
我觉得这样比较好  这样才是明智之举
I do think it's better this way. Yeah, we're being smart.
对  我肯定
Yes, I'm sure.
你真的肯定
You really sure?
我再回你电话
I'll call you back.
我们可以当炮友的
So we can be friends who sleep together.
没错  这不代表什么
Absolutely. This'll just be something we do.
就像打壁球一样
Like racquetball.
我觉得聪明又健康
Sounds smart and healthy to me.
不过出于好奇心
So just out of curiosity...
你现在还有其他打壁球的伙伴吗
do you currently have any other "racquetball" buddies?
只有你爸爸一个
Just your dad.
那是指真的壁球
Although that's actually racquetball.
我下周二
You know, I do have a blind date...
要和我妹妹的邻居约会
with my sister's neighbor next Tuesday.
你希望我取消吗
Do you want me to cancel it?
不要
No!
如果你取消  那就是为我取消的
Because if you did, that means you'd be canceling for me.
-而我们只是朋友  -没错
- And we're just friends. - Exactly.
不要坐
Oh, don't sit down.
-准备好做击球练习了吗  -那是当然
- You ready to go to the batting cage? - Yeah, You bet.
不过先送你一个礼物
And first, here's a gift.
紧身运动裤
Stretchy pants?!
世界上最好的东西
Those are the greatest things in the world!
如果我是你  我会天天穿  天天穿
If I were you, I'd wear them everyday every day.
谢谢  真的  你太体贴了
Gee, thank you. Really, that's so nice.
不过老实说  我觉得我穿不了
But, to be honest, I don't think I can wear these.
太紧了  我会觉得轮廓会被别人看到
They're so tight. I'd feel like I'm on display.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系  我再想办法...
That's all right. I'll figure....
大家好吗
How's it going?
很好
Good.
瑞秋  《闪灵》好不好看
Hey, Rach, how you doing with The Shining?
丹尼刚走进217号房
Danny just went into Room 217.
下面是最精彩的  浴缸里的死女人...
The next part's the best! That dead lady in the bathtub...
别说  拜托  这样就不好看了
No! Come on, you're gonna ruin it!
好吧  我用暗号说
All right, I'll talk in code.
记得小孩在走廊看到那两个空白吗
Remember when the kid sees those two "blanks" in the hallway?
对  那里很好看
Yeah, that's very cool.
所有的空白把空白弄成了空白空白
All "blank" and no "blank" makes "blank" a "blank-blank."
不  讲结局
No, the end!
杰克差点用空白杀了他们
When Jack almost kills them all with the "blank"...
不过到最后关头他们还是跑了
but in the last second, they get away.
乔伊  你居然做这种事
Joey, I can't believe you just did that.
她居然破解了你的暗号
I can't believe she cracked your code.
好吧  劳瑞跟乔求婚  她拒绝了
All right, okay. Laurie proposes to Jo and she says no...
即使她深爱着他
even though she's still in love with him.
他后来娶了艾美
Then he ends up marrying Amy.
喂  我不是存心要讲的
Hey, mine was by accident!
好吧  锅炉爆炸  烧毁旅馆
All right, the boiler explodes and destroys the hotel
那个爸爸也被烧死了
and kills the dad.
贝丝死了
Beth dies.
Beth dies?
真的吗  如果继续看下去贝丝就会死
Is that true? If I keep reading, is Beth gonna die?
不  贝丝不会死
No, Beth doesn't die.
她不会死  对不对瑞秋
She doesn't die. Does she, Rachel?
-什么  -乔伊问的是  你是不是毁了
- What? - Joey's asking if you just have ruined...
他喜欢的第一本
the first book he's ever loved
不是由杰克·尼克逊当主角的小说
that didn't star Jack Nicholson.
不  她不会死
No. She doesn't die.
那你干嘛这么说
Then why would you say that?
因为我故意要伤害你
Because I wanted to hurt you.
在这里  我的钥匙掉了
Oh, there they are. I dropped my keys.
找到了
Got them.
对不起  对不起
Sorry. I'm sorry.
你一定不敢相信我今天有多惨
You would not believe my day.
我上了两个班  雪上加霜的是
I had to work two shifts. And then to top it off...
我的一边假胸又被烤炉的火烧了
I lost one of my fake boobs in a grill fire.
你在笑什么
What are you smiling at?
我在想可能会柳暗花明又一村
I was thinking your day could still pick up.
你好
Hello.
我喜欢这种朋友关系
I love this "friend" thing!
罗伯特马上就要来了
Listen, Robert's gonna be here any second,
你们谁跟他说一声好吗
so could one of you just tell him?
拜托  马上说
Please, right now.
我一见他就想  那玩意儿是不是晃来晃去
Every time I see him, it's like, "is it on the loose?
是不是在看着我
Is it watching me?"
我们不能跟他说
We can't tell him.
你不能跟完全不熟悉的男人
You can't go up to a guy you barely know
谈论他的"那个"
and talk about his "stuff."
他说得对  就算是赞美也不行
He's right. Even if it's to say something complimentary.
可以去健身房了吗
So you ready for the gym?
有一面新的攀岩墙  我们可以互相照看
They got this new rock-climbing wall. We can spot each other.
我从这里就可以看到你
Yeah, I can spot you from here.
什么
What?
听我说  罗伯特
Okay, listen, Robert....
我们不是要...
Hey, don't we have to...?
对   我们要...
Yeah, we got....
我觉得你这个人真的很棒
I think you're really, really great.
老天  又来了
Oh, God. Here we go again.
为什么我老是发生这种事
Why does this keep happening to me?
我什么东西让你不高兴吗
Is it something I'm putting out there?
这是我的错吗  我很蠢吗(也指睾丸)
Is this my fault? Or am I just nuts?
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know what to say.
老弟  这地方老少皆宜
Hey, buddy? This is a family place.
把鸡鸡放回屋里去
Put the mouse back in the house.
真的  这间公寓很普通啊
Really? It's just like everyone else's apartment.
一样有房间  墙壁和天花板
It's got rooms and walls and ceilings.
我只是想看看你住的地方  带我参观下
I just wanted to see where you live. Now give me the tour.
我的天
Oh, my God!
-这里是客厅  -真舒适
- This is the living room. - That's nice.
-这里是厨房  -真漂亮
- And this is the kitchen. - That's real pretty.
等一下  我能参观卧室吗
Wait a minute. Don't I get to see the bedroom?
这是很普通的
Well, it's pretty much your typical...
卧室
bedroom.
我们还在门的这一边  我还没看到
We're still on this side of the door. I didn't get to see it.
要命  下次吧  今晚非常愉快
Oh, shoot. Maybe next time. Thanks for a lovely evening.
她是谁
So who is she?
就是我跟你说过的约会对象
That was the blind date that I told you about.
她打电话来改期到今天
She called and switched it from Tuesday.
你喜欢她吗
Did you like her?
我是以朋友的身份问的  因为我不会不高兴
I'm just asking as a friend, because I am totally fine with this.
你看起来是挺高兴的
Well, you seem fine.
好吧  我不高兴  我很不高兴
Okay, you know what? I'm not fine. I'm not.
我怎么高兴得起来  听到你跟她进来
I mean, how could I be fine? Hearing you come in with her.
她还想参观你的卧室
She wants to see your bedroom.
你知道吗
You know what?
我们或许可以做朋友
What if we're friends...
但不跟其他人交往
who don't see other people?
你是说"专属的"朋友
You mean like "exclusive" friends?
有何不可
Why not?
我是说  这周过的棒极了
I mean, this has been the most amazing week.
这也没什么不好吧
Would it be so terrible?
我们还可以一边做朋友  一边同居
Even if we were friends who lived together?
或许有一天
Or maybe someday,
可以站在其他朋友面前
friends who stood up in front of their other friends...
发誓当一辈子的朋友
and vowed to be friends forever.
我们又回到原点了
You know, we're back where we were.
亲爱的  我求之不得
Honey, I would love to do all that,
但一切都没有改变
but nothing's changed.
不是这样的  你把胡子刮掉了
That's not true. You don't have a moustache.
好吧  有一件事改变了
Okay, one thing's changed.
但我们的生活目标不同
But we still want different things,
我们都知道结局是什么
and we know how this is gonna end.
你知道吗
You know what?
我得马上离开这个房间
I gotta walk out of here right now.
因为忘记你是我一生中最困难的事
Because getting over you is the hardest thing I have ever had to do.
我想我再也做不到了
I don't think I could do it again.
我知道我做不到
I know I couldn't.
那么
So?
再打最后一场壁球怎么样
How about one last game of racquetball?
小心玫瑰刺
Watch the thorns!
怎么了
What?
贝丝病得很重
Beth is really, really sick.
乔在陪她  但我想她也无计可施
Jo's there, but I don't think there's anything she can do.
-乔伊  -干嘛
- Joey. - Yeah?
你要把书放进冰箱里吗
You wanna put the book in the freezer?
好办法
Okay.
好的